On Falling is a drama film directed by Laura Carreira.
Aurora, a Portuguese migrant, works as an order picker
in a warehouse in Edinburgh, Scotland.
Caught between the walls of a huge distribution centre and the solitude of her own room, Aurora tries to
seize every opportunity to resist the alienation and isolation that threaten her identity.
Aurora, played by Joana Santos.
Vera, played by Inês Vaz.
Agata, played by Olga Prokopenko.
Ian, played by Billy Reid.
Ben, played by Neil Leiper.
Dami, played by Damilare Akinrinmade.
On Falling is a 2024 social realist drama film, written and
directed by Laura Carreira and starring Joana Santos.
A British-Portuguese co-production, the film is Carreira's debut feature.
The film explores themes of class, kitchen sink realism,
gig economy, gritty, british social realism.
The tone is dark and emotional.